Welcome to the Driver menu of the controller of the domain layer!
Write the number of the option you want, or exit if you want to terminate the execution
	 0 -> Void constructor.
	 1 -> Void constructor with given item type, active user and algorithm.
	 2 -> Data load.
	 3 -> Change algorithm.
	 4 -> Recommend and DCG.
	 -1 -> close the driver menu.
Void constructor.


Void constructor with given item type, active user and algorithm


Data load.


Change algorithm. Please write the algorithm you want to use
(0 to use collaborative filtering, 1 to use content based)


Recommend and DCG. This case creates a new recommendation based on the algorithm given before.
This operation will take a few minutes, please keep waiting.
The items recommended are: [56949, 427, 502, 1381, 169, 69406, 65, 73, 839, 104374]
This recommendation's DCG is set to: 0.0


Change algorithm. Please write the algorithm you want to use
(0 to use collaborative filtering, 1 to use content based)


Recommend and DCG. This case creates a new recommendation based on the algorithm given before.
This operation will take a few minutes, please keep waiting.
The items recommended are: [909, 541, 905, 1376, 1672, 3019, 3087, 2926, 8981, 1283]
This recommendation's DCG is set to: 0.0


