Welcome to the Driver menu of ItemType!
Write the number of the option you want, or exit if you want to terminate the execution
	 1 -> ItemType()
	 2 -> ItemType((String nametype, ArrayList<String> attrib)
	 3 -> ItemType(String data)
	 4 -> String toString()
	 5 -> String getNameType()
	 6 -> ArrayList<String> getNameAttributes()
	 7 -> void setNameType(String nameType)
	 8 -> void setNameAttributes(ArrayList<String> nameattributes)
	 exit -> close the Driver menu
Constructor without attributes
nameType: 
nameAttributes: []
 
Constructor with nameType and attributes
Please, introduce your ItemType nameType (String)
Give the number of items to insert (INTEGER)
Please, introduce the nameTypes of the items reviewed by the ItemType (String)
nameType: Movies
nameAttributes: [Terror, Adult, Popularity, Mistery]
 
Constructor with a string given by the data domain.
Please, introduce your ItemType nameType (String)
Please enter the number of attributes that this type of item has. (INTEGER)
Please, introduce the name of the atributtes (String)
nameType: Anime
nameAttributes: [Gangsters]
 
Get the actual ItemType on string format
Anime¼Gangsters
 
Get the nameType of the initialized ItemType
nameType: Anime
 
Get the nameAttributes of the set in the  initialized ItemType, if there's none returns []
nameAttributes: [Gangsters]
 
Set the nameType of the initialized ItemType
Enter a valid nameType: (String)
 
Get the nameType of the initialized ItemType
nameType: Anime
 
Set the nameAttributes set of a itemType to the one of the initialized ItemType
Give the number of attributes to insert (INTEGER)
Enter a valid attributeName of nameAttribute: (String)
Enter a valid attributeName of nameAttribute: (String)
Enter a valid attributeName of nameAttribute: (String)
 
Get the nameAttributes of the set in the  initialized ItemType, if there's none returns []
nameAttributes: [Others, Isekai, Malice]
 
