Welcome to the Driver menu of User!
Write the number of the option you want, or exit if you want to terminate the execution
	 1 -> User()
	 2 -> User(Integer id)
	 3 -> User(Integer id, ArrayList<Integer> Reviews)
	 4 -> User(String data)
	 5 -> String toString()
	 6 -> Integer getId()
	 7 -> ArrayList<Integer> getReview()
	 8 -> void setId(Integer id)
	 9 -> void addReview(Integer id_item)
	 exit -> close the Driver menu
Constructor without attributes
Id: -1
ReviewsIds: []
 
Constructor with Id
Please, introduce your user id (INTEGER)
Id: 44
ReviewsIds: []
 
Constructor with Id and ReviewsIds
Please, introduce your user id (INTEGER)
Give the number of items to insert (INTEGER)
Please, introduce the ids of the items reviewed by the user (INTEGERS)
Id: 45
ReviewsIds: [34, 55, 2, 56]
 
Constructor with STRING (Id, and ReviewsIds)
Please, introduce your user id (INTEGER)
Give the number of items to insert (INTEGER)
Please, introduce the ids of the reviewed items (INTEGERS)
Id: 5
ReviewsIds: [45, 223, 2344]
 
Get the actual user on string format, if the user is not initialized returns -1
5¼45¼223¼2344
 
Get the id of the initialized user, if the user is not initialized returns -1
ID: 5
 
Get the ids of the reviewed items of the initialized user, if there's none returns []
ReviewsIds: [45, 223, 2344]
 
Set the id the initialized user
Enter a valid id: (INTEGER)
 
Get the id of the initialized user, if the user is not initialized returns -1
ID: 54354
 
Add the id of a item to Reviews of the initialized user
Enter a valid item id: (INTEGER)
 
Get the ids of the reviewed items of the initialized user, if there's none returns []
ReviewsIds: [45, 223, 2344, 5554]
 
