Welcome to the Driver menu of Pair!
	 1) -> Pair()
	 2)-> Pair(T1 key, T2 value)
	 3)-> T1 getKey()
	 4) -> T2 getValue() 
	 5) -> void setKey(T1 key) 
	 6) -> void setValue(T2 value) 
	 7) -> boolean equals(Pair<T1, T2> p)
	 8) -> Exit 
Please, choose an option with a new command
Constructor without attributes
The Key is null
The value is null


Please, choose an option with a new command
Constructor with the 2 parameters
Give the key
Give the id
The Key is 6
The value is 7


Please, choose an option with a new command
Get the information about the key of the Pair
The Key is 6


Please, choose an option with a new command
Get the information about the value of the Pair
The value is 7


Please, choose an option with a new command
Give the new key that you want
The Key is 12


Please, choose an option with a new command
Give the new value that you want
The value is 16


Please, choose an option with a new command
Give the key for the second pair
Give the value for the second pair
true


Please, choose an option with a new command
The DriverPair execution is finished, thanks for your time!
