Welcome to the Driver menu of ManagerRecommendation!
	 1) -> loadRecommendation(): ArrayList<String>
	 2) -> storeRecommendation(String id, String obj)
	 3) -> exit)
Specify the id of the active user: INTEGER number
50¼0.0


Please, specify the id of the active user: INTEGER number
Please, specify the DCG with comma (,).
Please specify the number of Item objects that you wanna store: Please, specify the Item ids that are recommended
50¼3.5¼88¼77


The DriverManagerRecommendation execution is finished, thanks for your time!
