Welcome to the Driver menu of Recommendation!
Write the number of the option you want, or exit if you want to terminate the execution
	 1 -> Void constructor.
	 2 -> Constructor with given id.
	 3 -> Constructor with given id and items.
	 4 -> Constructor with a string given by the data domain. Please insert the string, separated by '¼'
	 5 -> Constructor of the string of the object to be given to the data layer.
	 6 -> Getter of the identifier of the recommendation.
	 7 -> Getter of the user of the recommendation.
	 8 -> Getter of the items of the recommendation.
	 9 -> Getter of the DCG of the recommendation.
	 10 -> Setter of the id of the recommendation.
	 11 -> Setter of the DCG of the recommendation.
	 12 -> Setter of the DCG of the recommendation.
	 13 -> Setter of the items of the recommendation.
	 14 -> Adder of items.
	 15 -> Intersection of two recommendations.
	 16 -> Union of two recommendations.
Please give the next command.
Void constructor.
ID: -1, DCG: 0.0, items:


Please give the next command.
Constructor with given id.
ID: 50, DCG: 0.0, items:


Please give the next command.
Constructor with given id and items.
Give the number of items to insert
ID: 70, DCG: 0.0, items:
 5632
 1254


Please give the next command.
Constructor with a string given by the data domain. Please insert the id:
Now insert the DCG of the recommendation:
Finally, insert the items of the recommendation. When you want to end, type '-1':
ID: 6542, DCG: 9.3, items: []

Please give the next command.
Constructor of the string of the object to be given to the data layer.
6542¼9.3


Please give the next command.
Getter of the identifier of the recommendation.
Identifier: 6542


Please give the next command.
Getter of the user of the recommendation.
User: 6542


Please give the next command.
Getter of the items of the recommendation.
Items:


Please give the next command.
Getter of the DCG of the recommendation.
DCG: 9.3


Please give the next command.
Setter of the id of the recommendation. Give the id:
Id: 267


Please give the next command.
Setter of the user of the recommendation. Give the user:
User: 2


Please give the next command.
Setter of the DCG of the recommendation. Give the DCG:
DCG: 1.5


Please give the next command.
Setter of the items of the recommendation. Give the number of items:
Give the items of the recommendation:
 24
 25


Please give the next command.
Adder of items. Let's see the previous items given:
 24
 25
Give the new item to give:
Now, the items of the recommendation are:
 24
 25
 99


Please give the next command.
We give first the constructor for the first recommendation, then the second:
First constructor with given id and items. Give the id:
Give the number of items to insert:
ID: 5, DCG: 0.0, items:
 59
 536
 214
 52
Second constructor with given id and items. Give the id:
Give the number of items to insert:
ID: 99, DCG: 0.0, items:
 452
 214
 52
The intersection is:
ID: 5, DCG: 0.0, items:
 52
 214


Please give the next command.
Constructor with given id and items.
Give the number of items to insert
ID: 36, DCG: 0.0, items:
 75
 123
 556


Please give the next command.
Constructor with given id.
ID: 702, DCG: 0.0, items:


Please give the next command.
Constructor of the string of the object to be given to the data layer.
702¼0.0


Please give the next command.
Constructor with a string given by the data domain. Please insert the id:
Now insert the DCG of the recommendation:
Finally, insert the items of the recommendation. When you want to end, type '-1':
845
2136
1336
1236
ID: 888, DCG: 4.2, items: [845, 2136, 1336, 1236]

Please give the next command.
Constructor with given id and items.
Give the number of items to insert
ID: 36, DCG: 0.0, items:


Please give the next command.
Constructor with a string given by the data domain. Please insert the id:
Now insert the DCG of the recommendation:
Finally, insert the items of the recommendation. When you want to end, type '-1':
45
ID: 144, DCG: 2.3, items: [45]

Please give the next command.
